<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AUPF 2019</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>


    <string name="sabur_khan">"<html><body>Entrepreneur, ICT Personality and one of the inspiring nation builders of the country Mr. Md. Sabur Khan was born in the year 1965. He had an early interest to become Entrepreneur and very much concentrated on ICT arena. After completing his graduation and Post Graduation from Jahangir Nagar University, he started his business in the 1990. Now he is the Chairman of Daffodil International University (DIU) &amp; Daffodil Group which has been striving to be one of the leading ICT &amp; Education providers in Bangladesh. He is amongst those few leaders who worked silently for ICT Sector development during the early years of ICT’s orientation in Bangladesh. He has equal and very noteworthy contribution in the development of Education Sector as well.<br></br><br></br>"
        "Today Daffodil Group has about 20 concerns and operating in UK, USA, Dubai, Malaysia and in Bangladesh. He set his focus in the two areas:<br></br><br> </br>"
                "•ICT/ITES<br></br>"
                "•Education Sector<br><br></br></br>"
                "He is very much known as successful business entrepreneur, visionary leader and social contributor.\n</body></html>"
       </string>
    <string name="mahbubul_islam"><html><body>Educational Background: Winner of a number of awards, most of Professor Islam’s education was in UK. As a Commonwealth Scholarship holder, Professor Islam completed his PhD in Engineering from Strathclyde University, Glasgow in 1988. He was recipient of a David Livingstone award as well as a Charles Wallace award during his PhD research. Having stood first in his Master’s class he was recommended for an automatic transfer to the PhD program at Strathclyde University. He completed his Bachelor’s Degree in Electrical &amp; Electronic Engineering from Heriot-Watt University in Edinburgh in 1978 with 100% marks for his software project. To give a solid theoretical foundation to his existing teaching skills, he did a second Master’s in Instructional Design Technology from Open University Malaysia (OUM) completed in 2010 where his thesis pioneered a blended teaching model that combines the best of face-to-face teaching with e-Learning support that promotes deep reflection amongst learners. His work landed him with an adjunct professorship at OUM where he has been teaching Human Performance Technology (HPT) – a modern and complex subject.
        <br></br><br></br>Family Background: Professor Islam belongs to a family of academicians. His paternal grandfather Late Moulvi Serajul Islam was Professor at Rajshahi College from 1922 to 1947 and then till 1954 Professor at Chittagong College. Recipient of many awards, his father Professor Dr Ahmad Shamsul Islam guided more than 17 PhDs at the Department of Botany, Dhaka University, and established a two international journals and authored two books on Genetics that are used as textbooks. He was awarded the Curie Memorial Award in 1954 for his outstanding PhD research that developed “seedless strawberries” and was honored by the honorable Agriculture Minister Begum Matia Chowdhury during 2014 for initiating the work on the Jute Genome project. On the maternal side his grandfather Late Md. Sakhawat Hossain was the Founder President of Dhaka Chambers of Commerce &amp; Industry (DCCI) and a Founder Member of Dhaka Stock Exchange (DSE). His sister Dr Zeba Islam Seraj is Professor of Biochemistry who has a number of articles in peer reviewed journals to her credit, of which the article covering a salt resistant variety of rice is one.</body></html>"</string>
    <string name="mahbub_ul_haque_majumder"><html><body>Ph.D, 1988<br></br> ?>M. Sc. In Applied Chemistry (Specialization in Polymer Science), 1968<br></br>B. Sc. Honors in Chemistry, 1967
        <br></br><br></br>Attended Summer Science Institute in Chemistry (Jointly Sponsored by US Govt. &amp; The Then East Pakistan Govt.) held at The University of Dhaka, Chemistry, 1970 &amp; finished the course satisfactorily<br></br> Attended Imperial College of Science &amp; Technology, London as a British Council Fellow, Worked on a Polymer Project relating to the development of new types of membrane for use in artificial kidney machine, 1983<br></br>Attended Indian Institute of Science, Bangalore &amp; at IIT Madras, India as UNESCO fellow, Analytical Chemistry, 1987</body></html>"</string>
    <string name="muhammad_nuruzzaman">"<html><body>CEO, Daffodil Family and Convener of Daffodil ICT Carnival
        2018 and introducing all Concern Heads</body></html>"</string>
    <string name="mohamed_emran_hossain"><html><body>Designation: Assistant Professor<br></br>
        Department: Department of Development Studies<br></br>
        Faculty: Faculty of Humanities &amp; Social Science</body></html></string>
    <string name="mominul_haque_majumder"><html><body>Mr. Mominul Haque Majumder, previously Director (Finance &amp; Accounts) has joined as the newly appointed treasurer of Daffodil International University on August 26, 2019 as selected by the President of the People’s Republic of Bangladesh and Chancellor of Daffodil International University Mr. Abdul Hamid. He joined after Mr. Hamidul Haque Khan, the immediate past treasurer completed his term in the office successfully.<br></br>
        Mr. Mominul Haque Majumder completed his B.Com from University of Chittagong and M.Com from University of Dhaka. Besides this he also completed his MBA (Major in Finance) degree from Daffodil International University.<br></br>
        Mr. Mominul Haque Majumder started his career journey on January 01, 1988 in Bangladesh Rice Research Institute (BRRI). Later on he served for a long time in Bangladesh Rural Development Board (BRDB). He also served as Marketing Executive of Key Tech Private Ltd., Singapore. He joined Daffodil International University in 2002 as Deputy Director (Finance &amp; Accounts). He was promoted to the position of Director (Finance &amp; Accounts) in 2007 and continued till joining this position. He is the Founder President of DIU Alumni Association (DIUAA).<br></br>
        He was born on October 13, 1965 in a respectable Muslim family at Babur Hat in Chandpur Sadar Upazila. His father is late Mofiz Uddin Majumder and Mother is Late Mst. Johara Begum. He is blessed with three daughters.
        </body></html> </string>
    <string name="akm_fazlul_hoque"><html><body>Prof. Dr. Engr. A. K. M. Fazlul Hoque joined as Registrar of Daffodil International University on November 01, 2013. Before joining this position he had been serving as the Professor &amp; Head of the Department of Natural Sciences of Daffodil International University.
        He joined Daffodil International University as Adjunct Professor in CSE Department of Faculty of Science and Information Technology on February 01, 2011. Earlier he served as Director, Atomic Energy Centre, Dhaka (AECD) and as Head of Accelerator Facilities Division of AECD. He had thirty three years of research experience in Bangladesh Atomic Energy Commission (BAEC). He served as `Philips Research Fellow’ in the department of Applied Physics and Electronics of Dhaka University. He has been regularly supervising Ph. D, M. Phil, and M. Sc theses. He obtained M Sc in Applied Physics and Electronics from Dhaka University in 1976 and Ph. D in Physics (Nuclear Technology) from Jahangirnagor University in 2002. He had been graduated in Electrical Engineering (B. Sc Engg) from IEB in 198
    </body></html>
    </string>
    <string name="mostofa_kamal"><html><body>
        Academic Qualification<br></br><br></br>
        Ph.D (USA) in Real Estate Finance<br></br>
        MBA (UK) Major in Finance<br></br>
        M.Com. (Bangladesh) in Management<br></br>
        B.Com. (Honors) in Management
    </body></html></string>
    <string name="syed_akhter_hossain">"<html><body>Syed Akhter Hossain is a computer scientist, educator, columnist and technology consultant from Bangladesh. Currently he is a professor and head of Computer Science and Engineering department at Daffodil International University.<br></br>"
                "He is also a contest director of ACM-ICPC Dhaka Regionals 2007,2012 and Chief Judge of National Collegiate Programming Contest in Bangladesh 2015 and Contest Director of NCPC 2014.He is also the Chief Judge of ACM ICPC Dhaka Site2015 and one of the pioneers of spreading programming education in Bangladesh by organizing Computer Science Education Week and NGPC(National Girls Programming Contest). \n</body></html>"
     </string>
    <string name="touhid_bhuiyan"><html><body>Experienced Professor with a demonstrated history of working in the education management industry.
        Skilled in Cyber Security, Database, Big Data Analytics, Analytical Skills, Lecturing. Strong engineering professional with a Certificate focused in Cyber Security from University of Oxford.</body></html>"</string>
    <string name="shaikh_muhammad_allayear"><html><body>PhD in Computer Science, High Performance Computing, Anyang University, South Korea.
        Member of CCAP (Cross Culture Awareness Program). UNESCO (South Korea).</body></html>"</string>
    <string name="mohammad_shakhawat_hossain"><html><body>Principal,Associate Professor, <br></br>Dept of BBA
        <br></br><br></br>M.Com (Finance), MBA (Markting) DBA (In progress), DU</body></html></string>
    <string name="content_home">Daffodil ICT Carnival has been started in 2016 to bring all the talents among the students and represent them to the industry by commercialization. Since then, the event has been held with ICT based innovation, competitions, project showcase, counseling, mentoring, cultural events, learning opportunities, networking scope and many more so that every moment of the fest can be enjoyed and utilized with adding value. In line with this, DIU is proud to introduce and be the host of this mega event in Bangladesh and also planning to organize it in an innovative, effective and broader way to bring the best outcome. For more about Daffodil ICT Carnival 2019,
        please browse
    <a href="https://ictcarnival.daffodil.family/">https://ictcarnival.daffodil.family</a>
    </string>
    <string name="about_aupf">Originating from a friendly collaboration between institutions of higher education in China and Thailand, the Asian University Presidents Forum was officially established in 2002 to include higher education institutions across Asia. Since then, the forum has been held annually in different Asian countries and has fostered relationships and cooperation among participating institutions. In fact, cooperation is at the heart of the mission of the forum, whose mission is to “Increase Communication, Exchange Information, Share Experience and Seek Common Development.” Since its inception, AUPF has expanded throughout Asia and has congregated annually in different Asian countries. In line with this, DIU is proud to be the host of the forum in 2019 in Dhaka. DIU management warmly invites and welcomes participants from around the world to the 18 th Asian University Presidents’ Forum to be held in Dhaka, Bangladesh during November 22-24, 2019. This would be an incredible opportunity for the participants to interact and collaborate with other university presidents and leaders.
        \n\nFor more about  AUPF: <a href="http://www.aupf.net/">http://www.aupf.net/</a> </string>

    <string name="k_m_hasan_ripon">K. M Hasan Ripon
Adviser
Bangladesh Skill Development Institute (BSDI)
M +88- 01713-493206 | T+88-02- 8152105 
W www.bsdi-bd.org | S kmhasan.ripon</string>
    
    <string name="rathindra_nath_das">Executive Director,  DIPTI &amp; DTI</string>
    <string-array name="speakers_biography">
        <item>@string/sabur_khan</item>
        <item>@string/mahbubul_islam</item>
        <item>@string/mahbub_ul_haque_majumder</item>
        <item>@string/muhammad_nuruzzaman</item>
        <item>@string/mohamed_emran_hossain</item>
        <item>@string/mominul_haque_majumder</item>
        <item>@string/akm_fazlul_hoque</item>
        <item>@string/mostofa_kamal</item>
        <item>@string/syed_akhter_hossain</item>
        <item>@string/touhid_bhuiyan</item>
        <item>@string/shaikh_muhammad_allayear</item>
        <item>@string/mohammad_shakhawat_hossain</item>
        <item>@string/k_m_hasan_ripon</item>
        <item>@string/rathindra_nath_das</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
